[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bud Abbott and Lou Costello were a comedy team that lasted for 20 years, from the 1930s through the 1950s. What famous baseball routine are they best known for?", "correct_answer": "Whos on First?", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ump is Blind!", "Whos Playing Who?", "Whos your Daddy?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country, Slovakia or Slovenia, used to be part of Yugoslavia?", "correct_answer": "Slovenia", "incorrect_answers": ["Both", "Slovakia", "None of them"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the theme song from High Noon?", "correct_answer": "Do Not Foresake Me Oh My Darling", "incorrect_answers": ["Day of Reckoning", "High Noons AWaitin", "Only One Returns"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Latin proverb, Dum spiro, spero, mean in English?", "correct_answer": "While I breath, I hope", "incorrect_answers": ["Do to others the same as you do to yourself.", "I know that I dont know anything.", "Dont look a gift horse in the mouth."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of John Cusacks character in the 1984 classic comedy Sixteen Candles?", "correct_answer": "Bryce", "incorrect_answers": ["Cliff", "Jake", "Mike"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 48Hrs, Reggie, who has been incarcerated for a couple of years, has a large amount of money in the trunk of his car. How much money is in the trunk of Reggies car?", "correct_answer": "$500,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$100,000", "$300,000", "$250,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1980 movie Airplane had a star studded cast. Can you match the actor with the character he played?", "correct_answer": "Robert Stack - Rex Cramer", "incorrect_answers": ["Lloyd Bridges - Ted Striker", "Robert Hays - Dr. Rumack", "Peter Graves - McCroskey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie \u201cThe Last Emperor\u201d follows Puyis life from his ascension to the throne as a small boy to his imprisonment and political rehabilitation.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the first African-American pitcher in Major League Baseball.", "correct_answer": "Dan Bankhead", "incorrect_answers": ["Larry Doby", "Joe Black", "Don Newcombe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning movie directed by Oliver Stone featured Kevin Costner, Tommy Lee Jones, Gary Oldman and Joe Pesci?", "correct_answer": "JFK", "incorrect_answers": ["Alexander", "Heaven  Earth", "World Trade Center"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the driver of the limo Rosa enters in the movie 21?", "correct_answer": "An accomplice of Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Campbell", "Tom Cruise", "A random limo driver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Opel manufacture before it began making cars in 1899?", "correct_answer": "sewing machines and bicycles", "incorrect_answers": ["boats and steam engines", "televisions and motorcycles", "radio receivers and airplanes"]}]